Guide to the Lee P. Brown Papers, 1954-2013 MS 509
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series V: Atlanta Department of Public Safety Commissioner, 1978-1982, 42736
  - Subseries A: General, 42743
    - Managing Calls for Service, 1981-1982; 213345 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Management Development Program: Administrative Guidelines, 1981; 213347 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Management Reports, 1981; 213349 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Management System Reports, 1980; 213360 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Mayor Maynard Jackson's Inaugural Address, 1974-01-07; 213361 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Mental Health Task Force Community Action Forum, 1982; 213363 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Message from the Commissioner, 1978; 213364 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Multi-Jurisdictional Agreement, 1980; 213366 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Napper, George, 1980-1982; 213369 (Box 11, Folder 36-37)
    - Narrative Data on Organized Crime in Fulton County, 1978; 213372 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - National Institute of Corrections, 1979; 213374 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - National Organization of Black Law Enforcement Executives, 1981; 213379 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - National Urban League, 1978-1980; 213400 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - News Clippings, 1978; 213402 (Box 11, Folder 42-43)
    - News Clippings, 1979; 213420 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - News Clippings, 1980; 213421 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - News Clippings, 1981; 213422 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - News Clippings, 1982; 213423 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - News Media Policy, 1979; 213424 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - New Police Zones and Beats: A Basis for Neighborhood-Based Policing, 1982; 213425 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Notes, 1982; 213426 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Outside Employment Program, 1981; 213427 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Parking Lot Larcenies, 1979; 213428 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Parole Commission Guidelines, 1978; 213429 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - "Partnership Against Crime: The Key to a Safer Atlanta", ca. 1980; 213430 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Passport and Driver's License, ca. 1980; 213431 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Performance Evaluation system - Phase I Report, 1981; 213432 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - A Plan for Police Practices Advancement, 1980-1982; 213433 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Police/Community Action Agreements, 1981; 213434 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Police Executive Research Forum, 1978-1982; 213435 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Police Foundation, 1978-1980; 213436 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Police Officers' Rank and Years of Service, 1982; 213437 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Police Practices Advancement, 1981; 213438 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Police Recruitment, ca. 1980; 213439 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - "Police Use of Deadly Force: The Deadly Force Encounter" grant application, 1979; 213440 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Press Releases, 1978-1979; 213441 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Proceedings of the National Symposium on Higher Education for Police Officers, 1979; 213442 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Proposal for the Re-Organization of the Intelgence Section, 1978; 213443 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Public Safety in Atlanta, ca. 1980; 213444 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Public Safety Newsletter, 1979-1982; 213445 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Recruit Training Program Report, ca. 1980; 213446 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Report on Changing Watches, 1980; 213447 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - A Report on the Analysis of Ammunition Used, Firearms Control Police and Firearms Training within the Atlanta Police Bureau, 1982; 213448 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - The Revolutionary Communist Party, 1980; 213449 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Special Grand Jury Presentments - Five Year Plan for Improvement, 1980; 213450 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - State of the City, 1981; 213451 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - State of the Department Report, 1978; 213452 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - State of the Department Report, 1981; 213453 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Strategy for Crime Control in Atlanta, 1979; 213454 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Survey Regarding Officer Involved Shootings, 1981; 213455 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Task Force, ca. 1980; 213456 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Ten Percent Bail Program, 1979; 213457 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - TV-5 Editorials, 1978-1979, 1981; 213458 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Unit Audits, 1982; 213459 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Violent Crime: Who Are the Victims?, 1981; 213460 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Watson, Billy (Restricted), 1979; 213461 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Weekly Crime Prevention Tips, ca. 1980; 213462 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - "What About Crime in Atlanta?", 1979; 213463 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Youth Services Bureau Proposal, 1978; 213464 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Zone and Beat Redesign, 1981; 213465 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Subseries B: Articles, 42742
    - "Appropriate Firearms Policies", 1978; 213466 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - "The Atlanta Approach to Better Managing Demands for Police Services", 1981; 213467 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - "The Atlanta Bureau of Police Services: A Plan for Police Practices Advancement", 1980; 213468 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - "Atlanta Crime Information Network: Simple, Unique, and Inexpensive", 1981; 213469 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - "The Atlanta Criminal Information Network", 1980; 213470 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - "Black, Crime, and Justice", ca. 1980; 213471 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - "Comments on the Atlanta Business Chronicle's 'Survey of Crime'", 1980; 213472 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - "A Community Concern: Police Use of Deadly Force", 1979; 213473 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - "Crime Specific Planning: The Atlanta Experience", 1980; 213474 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - "Law Enforcement Initiated Crime Prevention and the Minority Community: History and Future", 1980; 213475 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - "Model Called-For-Service-Management Program", 1981; 213476 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - "National Black Police Association's Proposal to Survey the Perceptives and Experiences of Black Police Officers", ca. 1980; 213477 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - "New Directions in Law Enforcement", 1978; 213478 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - "An Organization and Management Review of the Lincoln Heights Police Department", 1978; 213479 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - "The Police and the Community", 1980; 213480 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - "Police Response to Ethnic Harrassment: The Atlanta Approach", 1982; 213481 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - "Pulse of the Public: Atlanta Crime Reporting Defended", 1980; 213486 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - "Research on Minority Communities: Toward an Understanding of the Relationship between Race and Crime" grant application, 1979; 213487 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - "Strategies for Controlling Crime (A Position Paper)", 1978; 213488 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - "The Victimizers", 1978; 213489 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - "White Collar Crime: The Atlanta Response", ca. 1979; 213490 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Subseries C: Atlanta Child Murders, 42741
    - Atlanta's Protect Our Children Campaign, ca. 1980; 213491 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Background Information and Status of Missing and Murdered Children, 1980-1981; 213492 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Briefing Materials - Volume I, 1980; 213493 (Box 13, Folder 8-9)
    - Chronology of Activities - Missing Children and Children Homicide Victims, 1980-1981; 213495 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - "The City It Always Wanted to Be: The Child Murders and the Coming of Age of Atlanta", 1997; 213496 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Community Correspondence, 1980; 213497 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1981; 213498 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Disappearances and Murders of Atlanta Children - Outline, 1980-11-21; 213499 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Fact Sheet Update, 1981; 213500 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - "Investigating the Psychopathic Killer", 1983; 213501 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - "Let's Keep Pulling Together Atlanta" campaign, 1981; 213502 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Mental Health Conference Remarks, 1981; 213503 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Missing and Murdered Children Briefing, 1981-03-04; 213504 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Napper, George, 1980-1981; 213505 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - News Clippings, 1979-1991; 213506 (Box 13, Folder 21-22)
    - Poem, 1981; 213508 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Review of Efforts, ca. 1981; 213509 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Town Hall Meeting, 1981-03-09; 213510 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Victim Information, ca. 1981; 213511 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Subseries D: Speeches, 42740
    - Albina Women's League Foundation, 1978-04; 213512 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Hungry Club Forum - Alpha Phi Alpha, 1978-05-17; 213513 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - "Contemporary Policing: The Best and Worst of Times", 1978-05-19; 213514 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Southern Christian Leadership Conference, 1978-05-20; 213515 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - West End Rotary Club, 1978-05-26; 213516 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - "An Agenda for Crime Control in the Black Community", 1978-05-27; 213517 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Georgia Association Security Personnel, 1978-05-30; 213518 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - "Black Organizations: An Agenda for Survival", 1978-06-03; 213519 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - United Youth Adult Conference, 1978-06-07; 213520 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Atlanta Street Academy Graduation Exercise, 1979-06-08; 213521 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - "Let Not Our Living Be in Vain!", 1978-06-18; 213522 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Lakewood Heights Business Men's Association, 1978-06-20; 213523 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Crime Prevention - Northside Kiwanis, 1978-06-23; 213524 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - First Annual Men's Day Program, 1978-06-25; 213525 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - NPU-F Planning Committee Meeting, 1978-06-26; 213526 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - "Appropriate Firearms Policies", 1978-06; 213527 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Men's Day - "Christian Men: Outreach Unlimited!", 1978-06; 213528 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Clark College Upward Bound Program, 1978-07-16; 213529 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - "The Black Church: An Agenda for Black Survival", 1978-07-21; 213530 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - "The Criminal Justice System: An Agenda for Change", 1978-07-29; 213531 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Youth Day Program Wright Street Baptist Church, 1978-07-30; 213532 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - "National Urban Policy: Its Impact on Criminal Justice", 1978-08-07; 213533 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - "The Black Family: An Agenda for Survival", 1978-08-13; 213534 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - "The Criminal Justice System: An Agenda for Change", 1978-08-17; 213535 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Chamber of Commerce - Downtown Council, 1978-08-18; 213536 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - "Correction in the Open: Interrelationships, Parternerships, Interdependency", 1978-08-22; 213537 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - 1978 Freshman Orientation Week - Morris Brown College, 1978-08-29; 213538 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - "Long Range Solutions to Urban Crime", 1978-08-29; 213539 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - "Police Stress: An Area of Concern", 1978-09-05; 213540 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Inaugural Exercises - D. M. Therrell High School, 1978-08-21; 213541 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - "Public Safety and the Black Community", 1978-08-26; 213542 (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Metropolitan Atlanta Juvenile Justice Program, 1978-09-27; 213543 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - U.S. Forest Service - Civil Rights Program, 1978-09-28; 213544 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - Walter White Elementary School, 1978-10-13; 213545 (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - National Association of Human Rights Workers - Community Relations Service Wokshop on Deadly Force, 1978-10-14; 213546 (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - Police Use of Deadly Force Conference, 1978-10-14; 213547 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - "Black People: An Agenda for Survival", 1978-10-16; 213548 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - Sandy Springs Rotary Club, 1978-10-16; 213549 (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - Atlanta Consular Corps, 1978-10-18; 213550 (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - Criminal Justice Career Day Program - Kennesaw College, 1978-10-18; 213551 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Atlanta Optimist Club, 1978-10-20; 213552 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Hungry Club Forum, 1978-10-25; 213553 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - City of Atlanta Employees Club, 1978-11-01; 213554 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - "For the Common Good", 1978-11-08; 213555 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Department of Public Safety Updates, 1978-11-11; 213557 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - "Major Issues in Today's Criminal Justice System", 1978-11-13; 213556 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - H. M. Turner HIgh School, 1978-11-15; 213558 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - "The Black Church: Its Mission for 1979", 1978-11-19; 213559 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - "Where Is Your Brother?", 1978-11-19; 213560 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Testimony before U.S. Parole Commission, 1978-12; 213561 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - "Black Organizations: An Agenda for Survival", 1978; 213562 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Antioch Baptist Church, ca. 1978; 213563 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Atlanta, Help Our Youth, Inc., 1979-01-20; 213564 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - "Crime and Rehabilitation", 1979-01-24; 213565 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Stone Mountain Correctional Facilities, 1979-01-28; 213566 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Atlanta Police Recruit Graduation, 1979-02-02; 213567 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - "America: A Look Into the Future", 1979-02-06; 213568 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - "Keeping the Dream Alive", 1979-02-08; 213569 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - "The Black Church: Its Mission for 1979", 1979-02-11; 213570 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - "Career Options in Protective Services", 1979-02-13; 213571 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - "Keeping the Dream Alive", 1979-02-14; 213572 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Atlanta Chapter Retired Officers Association, 1979-02-16; 213573 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Atlanta Area Technical School, 1979-02-21; 213574 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - "The New Generation", 1979-02-27; 213575 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Department of Public Safety, 1979-03-06; 213576 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - "A Challenge to the Parents", 1979-03-11; 213577 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - National Center for Leadership Development, 1979-03-11; 213578 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - NAACP - Annual Membership Campaign, 1979-03-12; 213579 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - "Men Dedicated to Christ", 1979-03-25; 213580 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Interagency Council of G. W. Carver Comprehensive High School, 1979-04-04; 213581 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Underground Atlanta Ribbon Burning Ceremony, 1979-04-10; 213582 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - "Public Safety in the Metropolitan Atlanta: Services and Problems", 1979-04-12; 213583 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha Fraternity, 1979-04-24; 213584 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Men's Effectiveness Sunday, 1979-04-29; 213585 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Booker T. Washington Evening High School Graduation, 1979-05-27; 213586 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Anderson Park Elementary School, 1979-06-05; 213587 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Afro-American Patrolmen's League, 1979-06-09; 213588 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - "Police Role in American Society", 1979-06-12; 213589 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Atlanta Police Academy, 1979-07-02; 213590 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - "The Black Church: Its Mission for 1980", 1979-07-15; 213591 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Kiwanis Club of Athens, 1979-07-19; 213592 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - "Crime", 1979-08-15; 213593 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - "Why Christian Concern for the Imprisoned", 1979-08-23; 213594 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - "An Opportunity in the Future", 1979-08-28; 213595 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - 10th Anniversary Celebration of Black Studies, 1979-08-28; 213596 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha Fraternity, 1979-10-14; 213597 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - "The Atlanta Experience: Its Impact on Law Enforcement and the Community", 1979-10-31; 213598 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Hungry Club Forum, 1979-10-31; 213599 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - East Lake United Methodist Church, 1979-11-03; 213600 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - National Association of Blacks in Criminal Justice, 1979-11-05; 213601 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Black American Law Student Association, 1979-11-06; 213602 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - "The Department of Public Safety", 1979-11-07; 213603 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - "Major Issues in Criminal Justice", 1979-11-12; 213604 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Atlanta Women's Chamber of Commerce, 1979-11-15; 213605 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Atlanta Police Academy Graduation, 1979-11-18; 213606 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Shoplifting Symposium Kick-Off, 1979-11-29; 213607 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - "The Meaning of Christmas", 1979-12-21; 213608 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - "Controlling Aggression", 1979; 213609 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - Taxicab Industry of the City in Atlanta, 1979; 213610 (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - "Violence, Crime: Solution" Conference Workshop, 1980-01-12; 213611 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - Crime Wave Symposium, 1980-01-15; 213612 (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - Georgia Tech Afro-American Association, 1981-01-22; 213613 (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - Hunter Hills AME Church, 1980-03-09; 213614 (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - American Business Women's Association, 1980-03-26; 213615 (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - National Honor Society Induction, 1980-03-27; 213616 (Box 14, Folder 66)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha - Annual Achievement Day, 1980-04-24; 213617 (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - Bureau of Fire Services Graduation, 1980-04-26; 213618 (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - Lee P. Brown Youth Award Banquet, 1980-05-18; 213619 (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - Tabernacle and New Canaan Baptist Church, 180-05-24; 213620 (Box 14, Folder 70)
    - "Crime in the Society", 1980-05-30; 213621 (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - "The Challenges of the 80's in Law Enforcement", 1980-06-14; 213622 (Box 14, Folder 72)
    - "To Be Followers of Christ: A Challenge for the 80's", 1980-06-15; 213624 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - "Solutions of Black on Black Crime", 1980-06-21; 213625 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - "Contemporary Crime Prevention: The Community and the Criminal Justice System", 1980-06-27; 213626 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - "Police Use of Excessive and Deadly Force: A Community Concern", 1980-07-16; 213627 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Sergeant James E. Richardson, Jr. Funeral Service, 1980-07-24; 213628 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - The Masons of William V. Banks Lodge, 1980-08-30; 213629 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Second Mount Vernon Baptist Church, 1980-08-31; 213630 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - "Police-Community Relations Reconsidered: What We Should Have Learned", 1980-10-19; 213631 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Bureau Police Services Graduation Ceremonies, 1980-10-31; 213632 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Thomasville Heights Community Leadership Awards, 1980-11-05; 213633 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Veteran's Day Celebration, 1980-11-11; 213634 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - "The Meaning of Christmas", 1980-12-18; 213635 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Bureau of Police Services Graduation Ceremonies, 1980-12-29; 213636 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Church of St. Jude Prayer, ca. 1980; 213637 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Department of Public Safety Annual Awards Ceremony, ca. 1980; 213638 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - The Effect of the Media on the Image of Crime in the Metropolitan Area, ca. 1980; 213639 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - The Hungry Club, ca. 1980; 213640 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Moral Values and Spiritual Influence in Crime Prevention, ca. 1980; 213641 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - "Current Issues and Trends of Today: Community Involvement", 1981-01-12; 213642 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Police Graduation, 1981-02-06; 213643 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Atlanta's Youth Against Crime, 1981-02-07; 213644 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Community Services Administration, 1981-02-11; 213645 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Criminal Justice Club and Student Government Association, 1981-02-12; 213646 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - American Business Women's Association, 1981-02-17; 213647 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Youth Development Center Drug Prevention and Education Program, 1981-02-19; 213648 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - "To Change Your World - You Must Change Your Mind", 1981-03-08; 213649 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Annual Men's Day Celebration, 1981-03-22; 213650 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Abolition of the Office of Juvenile Justice and Delinquency Prevention, 181-04-01; 213651 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Remarks Presented Before the Committee on Education and Labor, 1981-04-01; 213652 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Remarks Presented Before the Subcommittee on Juvenile Justice, 1981-04-01; 213653 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Atlanta Institute for Urban Affairs, 1981-04-10; 213654 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Ralph C. Robinson Boys Club, 1981-04-11; 213655 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Bureau of Fire Services Graduation, 1981-04-17; 213656 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Atlanta Jaycees Annual Dinner, 1981-04-23; 213657 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - "A Strong Family Life: Its Impact on Public Safety", 1981-04-25; 213658 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Police Memorial Day, 1981-05-15; 213659 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Atlanta Speech Program, 1981-05-17; 213660 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - "The Role of Christian Men as Builders of Tomorrow", 1981-05-17; 213661 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Testimony Presented Before the U.S. Attorney General's Task Force on Violent Crime, 1981-05-20; 213662 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Committee on Education and Labor Committee, 1981-03; 213667 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Federal Initiatives on Crime Control, 1981-06-30; 213676 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Testimony Presented Before the Subcommittee on Crime of the House Committee on the Judiciary, 1981-06-30; 213677 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - "Violent Crime in America: A Call for Action", 1981-07-14; 213678 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Police Graduation, 1981-07-27; 213679 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Radcliffe Presbyterian Church, 1981-08-09; 213680 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - The Georgia Annual Conference of the CME Church, 1981-08-11; 213681 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - "The Atlanta Bureau of Police Services: Calls-for-Service Management Program", 1981-09-24; 213682 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Congressional Black Caucus - Criminal Justice Braintrust, 1981-09-25; 213683 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - "The Police Use of Excessive and Deadly Force", 1981-09-25; 213684 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - "The Black Church in 1980 America", 1981-09-27; 213685 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - "Public Safety in Urban Affairs", 1981-10-05; 213686 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Southeast Regional Trade Show Awards Banquet, 1981-10-10; 213687 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Morris Brown College 100th Anniversary Celebration, 1981-10-16; 213688 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Buearu of Fire Services Graduation, 1981-11-25; 213689 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - "Peace of the City", 1981-12-04; 213690 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Emergency Medical Services Training Ceremony, 1981-12-10; 213691 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - "National Consultant Comments: Peace of the City Task Force Interim Report", 1981; 213692 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Atlanta Water Works Retired Officers Roundup, ca. 1981; 213693 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - "The Effect of the Media on the Image of Crime in the Metropolitan Area", 1982-01-12; 213694 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - "More Than Just an Average Man", 1982-01-18; 213695 (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - "Violence: A Concern in the Minority Community", 1982-01-30; 213696 (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - "What's Happening America?", 1982-01-30; 213697 (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - "Police Response to Ethnic Harassment: State-of-the-Art", 1982-01-31; 213698 (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - Department of Public Safety Annual Report, ca. 1982-01; 213699 (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - "Progressiveness in the Midst of Adverse Times", 1982-02-10; 213700 (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - "Federal Assistance to State and Local Law Enforcement", 1982-02-11; 213701 (Box 15, Folder 66)
    - "What Will Your Legacy Be?", 1982-02-18; 213702 (Box 15, Folder 67)
    - "Police Response to Ethnic Harassment: The Atlanta Approach", 1982-02-22; 213703 (Box 15, Folder 68)
    - "Crime and Justice in an Age of Scarcity", 1982-02-25; 213704 (Box 15, Folder 69)